blogsat360.com 2014-04-17

# India Entertainment Blog | Fashion | Business | Lifestyle | Bollywood | Technology » PRIVACY POLICY

## by KIRAN SHETH

**Our Commitment**  
Blogsat360.com  is strongly committed to your right to privacy and to keeping your personal information secure. To earn your trust and confidence in our commitment, we are fully disclosing our privacy practices. We encourage you to read our privacy statement to understand what types of personally identifiable information we collect and how we use this information.

Information collected by Blogsat360.com and how it is used  
Blogsat360.com only collects the necessary personally identifiable information in order to respond to your requests for our customized products and services. Personally identifiable information includes, but is not limited to, first and last name, physical address, e-mail address, phone number, birth date, and any other information that itself identifies or when tied to the above information, may identify you as a specific individual.

This website does not collect personally identifiable information about you except when you specifically and knowingly provide it. Blogsat360.com and its service partners use your personally identifiable information to operate the sites and services and to inform you of new features, services, and products from Blogsat360.com and its affiliates.

Blogsat360.com may also carefully select other companies to send you information about their products or services which are related to the site’s service but are not necessary to its operation (an “Extended Service”). If Blogsat360.com intends to use personally identifiable information for an Extended Service, the Blogsat360.com site will provide you with the ability and requisite instructions to decline this service. You may also stop the delivery of informational or promotional mail from Blogsat360.com by following the instructions on the mail.

Blogsat360.com may disclose personally identifiable information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (i) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on the site or its owners; (ii) protect and defend the rights or property of the site-owners, the site or the users of Blogsat360.com, and (iii) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Blogsat360.com, the site, its owners, or the public.

• Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to your website.

• Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.

• Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the advertising opt-out page. (Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page.)

If you have not opted out of third-party ad serving, the cookies of other third-party vendors or ad networks may also be used to serve ads on your site, and should be disclosed in your privacy policy as well in the following manner.

• Notify your site visitors of the third-party vendors and ad networks serving ads on your site.

• Provide links to the appropriate vendor and ad network websites.

• Inform your users that they may visit those websites to opt out of cookies (if the vendor or ad network offers this capability). Users can opt out of some, but not all, of these cookies in one location at the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out website at[www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

**Other Websites**  
The Blogsat360.com site contains links to other websites. Blogsat360.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.

**Notify Us**  
If at any time you believe that Blogsat360.com or its users/members have not adhered to these principles, please notify Blogsat360.com by e-mail at contact@blogsat360.com and we will use all commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and correct the problem.
